Hi, my name is Mandepulu. I'm a
financial advisor at Credential Life
Assurance. So, I've been with Credential
for 4 years now and uh the greatest
pleasures that I take in being with
Credential is being able to advise
clients on how to invest and just making
sure they have a future for their little
ones. Apart from that, credential has
exciting things that it does for us
being a consultant and you get to
qualify for these clubs, different clubs
starting from diamond league, uh, MGRT
and, uh, President Club and the like.
So, I have been I've had the opportunity
to qualify for different clubs, almost
all of them. So I've done uh MDRT which
is been amongst the 5% world's most best
uh financial advisors in the world of
course and then also I have been able to
qualify for coot I was the first one to
do coot in the country which makes me
very proud and also I have been the
first one to do president club um in the
country as well. So I would advise
people to join credential not only to
qualify for clubs and travel but also to
make their lives better. This is
something that has enabled me to do
different things. I've been able to get
land. I've been able to do things that I
never expected to do. So join credential
and try and build your life better.
[Music]